Guide to the National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets 1945-1969
National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets, 1945-1969
5340
National Association of Manufactures (NAM)
3 linear ft.
Pamphlets, records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Tracts and pamphlets on topics related to the labor question and the free enterprise system. Also included are a sample of NAM periodical literature and releases of the NAM Press Bureau.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Tracts and pamphlets on topics related to the labor question and the free enterprise system. Also included are a sample of NAM periodical literature and releases of the NAM Press Bureau.
SUBJECTS
Names:
National Association of Manufacturers (U.S.)
Subjects:
Labor unions -- United States.; Industrial relations -- United States.; Unemployment insurance -- United States.
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Records (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- NAM Publications, 1908-1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of Committee on Open Shop, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1925. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Law's Supremacy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Address of John Kirby, Jr., Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By John Kirby, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Legal and Historical Progress of Trade Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Hon. Jesse Holdom. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Closed Shop Unionism, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Walter Drew. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Wealth, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By George E. Sokolsky. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: What the Future Holds for the American System of Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By J. Howard Pew. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What Does Capital Want for Itself and America?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Charles R. Hook. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Open Shop "Conspiracy", Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Samuel Gompers, Samuel Harden Church, John E. Edgerton. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What Does the Closed Shop Mean to You?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Collective Bargaining A Management Guide, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Law Department Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 7/5/1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Law Department Memorandum, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 26,1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Supplement to NAM Law Digest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Law Department Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Law Department Memorandum Patman Robinson Price Discrimination Bill, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Supplement to NAM Law Digest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Labor Relations Bulletin Could Your Company Absorb Additional Taxes?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Labor Relations Bulletin Detail of New Social Security Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin Federal Unemployment Compensation Tax, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 13, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin A Community of Interest, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 20, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin On the Way to the Top, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 18, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin A Strike Settlement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 20, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin Federal Social Security Act Manual, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 7, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 1/22/1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin Social Security Act Notes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 25, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin Answers to Questions on the Wagner Act, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 25, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 15, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 15, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: NAM Labor Relations Bulletin Labor Responsibility, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 23, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Supplement to Labor Relations Bulletin: Some Notes on Employment Records, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- NAM Publications, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Seventh NAM Institute on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 23-26, 1943. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1939-1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Management, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Victory for Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: War Program of American Industry and Resolutions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Economic Background for Social Action, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Faith In Our Country, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Howard Coonley. 12/6/1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining The Legal Enforceability, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Second Report of the Postwar Committee of the NAM, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Industrial Health Practices, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. October 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Relation of Government to Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: War Control of Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Today Production for Victory Tomorrow Opportunity Jobs Freedom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Employment Regularization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NAM Publications, 1939-1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Victory Institute on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Keeping Fit for a Profit, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Dr. Victor G. Heiser. September 26, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Why Employment Relations?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: NAM Wartime Institute on Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 24-28, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Industry's Program for American Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NAM Publications, 1935-1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Public Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By John E. Edgerton. 1/27/1931. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Public Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March, 1930. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Compulsory Public Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By James A. Emery. 2/18/1931. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Some Observations on British Experience in the Field of Employment Relations and Social Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By John C. Gall. December, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Should There Be Federal Legislation Controlling Hours and Wages?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 7/15/1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Points Against Compulsory Public Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/5/1932. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Special Bulletin on the Wagner-Connery Bill, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 3/12/1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What's Behind the Hue and Cry About Profits?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Frederick C. Crawford. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Public and Employee Attitudes on Labor Problems, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Noel Sargent. August 24-28, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Government's Place in Postwar Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By H.W. Prentis, Jr. 1/20/1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Significance of Agitation for Public Old Age Pensions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Noel Sargent. 6/12/1930. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Economic Old Age- Industry Looks at the Problem, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Noel Sargent. 6/13/1930. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Industrial Care of the Long-Service Worker, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Noel Sargent. 10/15/1929. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Platform of American Industry for 1928, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Thirty-Hour Work Week, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By James A. Emery. 1/17/1933. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: At School- Not at Work, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Cooperative Education and Other Work-Study Plans, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. January 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: NAM Looks at Cartels, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Financing Small Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Nathan Report CIO Campaign for Higher Wages, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: The Public and Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Should Labor Be Given A Direct Share In the Management of Industry?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 11/18/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Facts vs. The Nathan Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Ralph Robey. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Nathan Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Now- Let's Build America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Robert R. Wason. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Nam's Public Relations Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Holcombe Parkes. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: An Appraisal of NAM's Public Relations Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By H. Howard Pew. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Make Way for Prosperity, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/3/1946. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1928-1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Production Outlook for the Oil Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Eugene Holman. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Production Outlook for the Steel Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Charles R. Hook. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Outlook for the Machine Tool Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Robert M. Gaylord. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Production Outlook for the Automobile Industry, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By B.E. Hutchinson. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Behind the Iron Curtain, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By George Moorad. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What Are We Waiting For?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Dr. Raymond Moley. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Government and Business, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By W. Averell Harriman. 12/4/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: An Address By, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Douglas MacGregor. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Occupied Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Lt. Gen Lucius D. Clay. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Relations Session, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Forney Johnston. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Changes in Wage Trends, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Leo Wolman. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Portal-to-Portal Issue, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Raymond S. Smethurst. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A New Federal Labor Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Clarence B. Randall. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: A National Labor Relations Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Senator Joseph H. Ball. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Public Wants Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Mrs. LaFell Dickinson. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Business Bites Budget, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Lane D. Webber. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Making Regular Jobs Regular, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Ira Mosher. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Note to Editors, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Domestic Monopolies and International Cartels, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By H.H. Schell. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: A National Labor Relations Policy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Merchandising Free Enterprise, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Holcombe Parkes. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: How To Get Useful Industrial Information from Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Charles S. Weaver. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: How To Get Useful Industrial Information from Germany, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By John C. Green. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Employment Act and the Economic Future, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Dr. Edwin G. Nourse. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: France and World Reconstruction, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Alexandre Parodi. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Liberty Pays Off, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By William Harry Chamberlin. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Securing the Ideals for Which We Fought, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Paul H. Griffith. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Ideologies and World Peace, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Jan Christiaan Smuts. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Training for Democratic Ideals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Dr. Edmund Ezra Day. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
- NAM Press Releases, 1939-1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Should Labor Be Given A Direct Share In the Management of Industry?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Good Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: A Key to More Jobs, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Tariff, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Who Profits from Profits?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Wallace F. Bennett, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 53: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 54: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 56: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/4/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 58: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 59: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 60: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 5/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 5/3/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 4/14/1947. Item is in English.
- NAM News, 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: NAM News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/5/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: NAM News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/6/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: NAM News, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/7/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Unbeatable Partnership, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Cloud Wampler. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: What Research is Doing For You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Dr. Robert A. Millikan. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Opening Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Don G. Mitchell. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Canadian Federal Sales Tax, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By R.N. McCormick. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: A General Manufacturer's Excise Tax, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Lothair Teetor. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: What Is Happening In the Patent Office, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Lawrence G. Kingsland. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A General Manufacturer's Excise Tax, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Harley L. Lutz. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: A General Manufacturers' Excise Tax, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Arthur R. Kaiser. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Reasons for Preferring Taxes on Selected Commodities to a Tax on All Manufacturers, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By C. Lowell Harriss. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: What is Happening in the Field of Rockets, Jet Propulsion, and Supersonic Flight, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By General Joseph T. McNarney. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications (1 of 2), 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: That New Labor Law, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: One World- or Two?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Rep. Walter H. Judd. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Focus on World Finance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Robert L. Garner. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Spotlight on Job Security "The American Dream", Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Wallace F. Bennett. 12/2/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: We Owe It To America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Morris Sayre. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Teamwork for Prosperity, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Charles Sawyer. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Inflation and Its Implications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Earl Bunting. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Miracle of 1948, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Wheeler McMillen. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: For NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By E.J. Thomas. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Your Future Is What You Make It, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Rev. Norman Vincent Peale. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Inflation and its Implications, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By B.E. Hutchinson. 12/3/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Government's Place on the Team, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By Ira Mosher. 12/1/1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Interlocking Economies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)